kitchengardeners.org 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Kitchen Gardeners International

Kitchen Gardeners International (KGI.org) is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using our website. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit KGI.org.

**Information We Collect**  
We may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, age, address, e-mail address, and other information. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. In addition, we may conduct occasional online surveys. These surveys are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate. Furthermore, we automatically collect non-personally identifiable IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit KGI.org.

**How We Use Information Collected**  
We may use information: (i) for the purposes for which you specifically provided the information, (ii) to send you e-mails only relating to KGI.org unless you have opted out of receiving such e-mail, (iii) to enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services, and (iv) to provide other third parties with aggregate (non-personally identifiable) information about our user base and usage patterns. We will not share your personally identifiable information outside of KGI.org unless you “opt in” to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us. However, we may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Terms of Use or when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.

**Blogging, Comments and Social Networking**  
The blogging, comments functions of KGI.org allow you to post your own articles and to comment on what other readers have to say. When you use these features (for example, by posting to a blog or making a comment), you may be making public any information that you provide including your name, location and e-mail address.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use cookies to allow you to move quickly through our site, to recognize repeat visitors and to allow you to take advantage of some of our site’s special features. A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a Web site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer’s memory. Cookies are small files (just a few hundred bytes) and won’t pose any significant disk-space concerns. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by KGI.org only and does not cover the use of cookies or web beacons by any third-parties.

**Links**  
The Services may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that KGI.org is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Security**  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your KGI.org information is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, KGI.org uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.  
Further, KGI.org retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
KGI.org may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of the KGI.org website after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.
